<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on Hello Friend</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on Hello Friend</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 21:36:03 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>whoami</title>
      <link>/whoami/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 21:36:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/whoami/</guid>
      <description> Me? I know who I am. I&amp;rsquo;m a dude playing a dude disguised as another dude.
&amp;mdash; Kirk Lazarus
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 21:23:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>A page about me!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Encypted Cross Platform Notes</title>
      <link>/posts/encrypted-cross-platfor-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 12:39:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/encrypted-cross-platfor-notes/</guid>
      <description>Challenges I&amp;rsquo;ve tried multiple note taking solutions, including OneNote, Dropbox, Quip, GDrive, Evernote, .txt files, cherrytree, and others. They all work great in some ways, fall short in others. None work platform independent.
Requirements Portability
 Accessible from any machine with or without a browser No service, software, or OS lock in Configure what notes are synced and what notes are only accessible locally  Private
 I shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have to agree to have them indexed by a 3rd party End to end encryption  Nice to haves  vi keybindings Rich formatting Export to different formats, including markdown and pdf Same environment on any workstation Works offline  Enter Spacemacs + Org Mode + GnuPG Spacemacs is emacs pre-configured with a host of plug-ins, including emacs-evil, and extensible vi layer that add vi keybindings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Spacemacs &amp; GnuPG on Windows 10</title>
      <link>/posts/install-spacemacs-and-gnugp-on-windows-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 12:22:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/install-spacemacs-and-gnugp-on-windows-10/</guid>
      <description>Requirements  chocolatey git  Using the chocolatey package manager and git, we are going to get everything up and running.
choco install  First, we need to open powershell or cmd in administrative mode
 Next, install Emacs, the Source Code Pro font, and gpg4win with chocolatey with the following command
   choco install spacemacs gpg4win sourcecodepro  Now to add Spacemacs to our Start Menu  Press win key and search for runemacs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archive</title>
      <link>/archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/archive/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>